brave.com 2016-11-08

# Brave Software | Privacy Policy

#### Last Updated March 4, 2016

#### 

  * Privacy in our software
  * Privacy on our website

## Software Privacy

This privacy statement describes how our suite of Brave browsers for iOS, Android, macOS and Windows “ **Brave** ”, (“ **Brave** ”, “ **us** ”, “ **we** ” and/or “ **our** ”) collect and use the personal information you provide through Brave. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. Note, this privacy statement covers your use of the Brave browsers only. If you are visiting the Brave Software web site or using other Brave Software products or services, additional terms may apply.

## Overview

Brave is not in the business of selling personal information about you. We believe the best way to ensure your private information is protected is to make every effort to ensure we are not receiving your private information in the first place.

## Collection & Use

#### Brave for iOS and Brave for Android:

We use a third party application performance analytics provider called Crashlytics to collect crash report data and other data about the usage of Brave. We do not store any user identifiable data, nor IP address, nor unique IDs. For more information on the type of data Crashlytics collects through Brave and how that data is used, please visit <https://answers.io/img/privacy.pdf>. The data collected by Crashlytics is provided to Brave in aggregated form through a crash report – the report contains information about crashes, specifically what kind of device was being used when Brave crashed and which version was in use during the crash. We use these reports information to improve the overall performance of Brave. These crash reports do not include personally identifiable information or other personal account information.

#### Brave for macOS and Windows:

We collect user data regarding crashes and requests for updates. We do not store any personally identifiable data of our users, IP addresses, or unique IDs. We send a request to our server to see if an update is available and whether it was the first ever, first daily, first weekly, or first monthly request. These requests do not rely on third party software. We use a Node.js heroku server, which is based on Electron.

## Tracking & Ads

Brave and our advertising partners may provide ads to you through Brave when you have enabled the Ad Replacement feature (which is the default setting in any of our browsers). These Ads do not use tracking technologies like cookies or any other persistent storage on your browser. Browsing history and other information that is used to generate intent signals is encrypted using a client generated key such that Brave cannot see or use this information for any purposes other than Ad Replacement. The encrypted data is stored by Brave for the sole purpose of syncing across the User’s devices that utilize a Brave browser, but Brave does not have access to the client generated key that can be used to decrypt the data and therefore cannot “read” or “see” this data. If you choose to disable the Ad Replacement or Ad Blocking features available through Brave’s settings, this may allow third party cookies and persistent storage technologies to collect information about you and your browsing activities. This may include collection of your personally identifiable information, but Brave does not receive or use this information.

Brave will also collect anonymous ad campaign related data that will be used for reporting and payments to third parties. This includes payments to both ad publishers and Brave partners for Ads viewed by you using Brave Ad Replacement. This data cannot be linked to your device(s) or otherwise identify you. Brave will not collect any information for ads that are delivered when Ad Replacement or Ad Blocking is not enabled.

## Privacy on our Website

Privacy policy for website is pending final legal review. Please contact us at [info@brave.com](mailto:info@brave.com) with questions.

## Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (if you have voluntarily signed up for updates via email), and we will also include a notice on our website at [https://brave.com](https://brave.com/). Your continued use of Brave after any changes or revisions to this privacy statement shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised privacy statement.

## Contact

You can contact us about this privacy statement by emailing [support@brave.com](mailto:support@brave.com). We are also available and responding to you questions and concerns at [twitter.com/Brave](https://twitter.com/Brave) and at [Github.com/Brave](https://github.com/Brave).
